Guide to the New Dramatists Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, 1949-1996; Series II; 114.58; (100 boxes) + 12 broadside folders
  - Financial Records
    - Generals, 1984 (Box 54)
    - University of Miami, 1984; 2 (Box 54)
    - Workshops, undated (Box 54)
    - Press releases, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Readings, 1984 (Box 54)
    - ScriptShare, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Directors, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Writers Executive Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
    - Mercantile Library of the City of New York, 1982 (Box 54)
    - Press, agents, undated (Box 54)
    - Staff and board, 1982-1983 (Box 54)
    - ScriptShare scene night, undated (Box 54)
    - Non-performance workshop, undated (Box 54)
    - Cast contact sheet for "Welcome to Sodom and Gomorrah", undated (Box 54)
    - McDonalds, undated (Box 54)
    - Cast contact sheets for "No More Summers", "Gym Rats", and "The Bulldog and the Bear", undated; 3 (Box 54)
    - January project, 1983 (Box 54)
    - General auditions, 1983 September (Box 54)
    - Actor presentations and design portfolio review for the League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Contributors, 1984 (Box 54)
    - Weekend retreat, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Budget, undated (Box 54)
    - Internship forms, undated (Box 54)
    - Readings, 1983-1988 (Box 54)
    - Member bulletins, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Public relations: general, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Wylie, Stephen, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
    - Admissions, 1983 Fall (Box 54)
    - Celebrity bios, undated (Box 54)
    - Off Off Broadway Alliance, undated (Box 54)
    - Member's activities, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Admissions, 1979-1983 (Box 54)
    - Readings, undated (Box 54)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 54)
    - Alliance of Resident Theatres, 1983 (Box 54)
    - Production, 1983-1984 (Box 54)
    - General auditions, 1982 September (Box 54)
    - Cast contact sheets, undated (Box 54)
    - List of actors, undated (Box 54)
    - Stage manager, 1984 (Box 55)
    - First stage - exchanges (Box 55)
    - Musical theatre general auditions, undated (Box 55)
    - "We Do It All for You", undated (Box 55)
    - Old audition schedules, 1982-1984 (Box 55)
    - Alumni news, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Playwright's platform "Boston", undated (Box 55)
    - Intern program, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Alumni column, 1983-1984 (Box 55)
    - Alumni information, 1983-1984 (Box 55)
    - Intern development, undated (Box 55)
    - Internship information, 1985-1986 (Box 55)
    - State of the union - budgets, etc., 1985 (Box 55)
    - Seventh heaven, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Library, undated (Box 55)
    - Readings: printing estimates, 1983-1984 (Box 55)
    - Member's bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box 55)
    - Internships, undated (Box 55)
    - Mailing list additions, undated (Box 55)
    - Expect to join, undated (Box 55)
    - Apple computer proposal, undated (Box 55)
    - Archive newsletters, undated (Box 55)
    - Admissions, undated; 4 (Box 55)
    - Staff and board, 1984-1985 (Box 56)
    - General auditions, 1984 September (Box 56)
    - Survey of archival material with photographs of building, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Actor presentations and design portfolio review for the League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Classes, 1983-1984 (Box 56)
    - State of the union, undated (Box 56)
    - Radio and television, 1984-1987 (Box 56)
    - New York Theatre Studio, undated (Box 56)
    - Aspen Playwrights Conference, undated (Box 56)
    - Producers, 1984 (Box 56)
    - Press forms, 1985 (Box 56)
    - General auditions, 1985 January (Box 56)
    - Members' bulletin, 1985 December (Box 56)
    - Auditions, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Opera workshop, 1985 (Box 56)
    - ScriptShare, 1985; 2 (Box 56)
    - Therriault, Daniel, undated (Box 56)
    - "Not Showing" by Ryan, James, 1985 (Box 56)
    - "Red Storm Flower" by Shanley, John Patrick, undated (Box 56)
    - Members - Marsha Norman speech, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Newsletter, 1985 (Box 56)
    - List of residencies awarded to the members of New Dramatists, 1985 March (Box 56)
    - ScriptShare letters to file, 1985 (Box 56)
    - ScriptShare responses, undated (Box 56)
    - Levi, Stephen, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Press, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Members - class flyers, undated (Box 56)
    - Press correspondence, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Press releases rough draft, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Admissions - requests to send, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Admissions - rejection letters, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Production, undated (Box 56)
    - Members' activities, 1985 Summer (Box 56)
    - Ballots and surveys, undated (Box 56)
    - Budget comparisons, 1986-1988 (Box 56)
    - Mailing list - actors, undated (Box 56)
    - Information for the bulletin, undated (Box 56)
    - Bulletin, 1985 September (Box 56)
    - Stage director applications, undated (Box 56)
    - Members - activity sheets, undated (Box 56)
    - ScriptShare - agent updated, 1985 (Box 56)
    - ScriptShare - scripts owned, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Press - Bainum, Mibs, 1983 (Box 56)
    - Press - lists, undated (Box 56)
    - Press - activities, undated (Box 56)
    - Newsletter, 1985 September (Box 56)
    - Admissions - rejection letters, 1982-1983 (Box 57)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 57)
    - Press plan, 1985 (Box 57)
    - No publication drafts, undated (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Bowne, Alan, undated (Box 57)
    - Applicants, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Material for board, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Playwright profiles, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Press, undated (Box 57)
    - Playbill for "True West" by Shepard, Sam, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Members' bulletin, undated (Box 57)
    - Northlight Theatre, undated (Box 57)
    - Members' bulletin, 1985-1985 (Box 57)
    - Plays for ScriptShare, undated (Box 57)
    - Writers' Executive Committee, 1984-1985; 2 (Box 57)
    - Members' bulletin, 1986 May (Box 57)
    - Playwriting class, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
    - Cristina Crawford Foundation, 1986 (Box 57)
    - "Celebrity Doodles, Drawings & Designs" auction, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Literary managers, undated (Box 57)
    - Clemson University, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Membership bulletin, 1986 January (Box 57)
    - Actor presentations and design portfolio review for the League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Staged readings, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Members' bulletin, 1986; 2 (Box 57)
    - General auditions, 1986 Fall (Box 57)
    - Finalists, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Artist's fellowship guidelines, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
    - Internship information and application, undated; 2 (Box 57)
    - Internship contacts and information sent, 1987 Summer (Box 57)
    - Internship packet, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Illinois Arts Council, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Press lists, undated (Box 57)
    - Temple University actor presentations, undated (Box 57)
    - Production, undated (Box 57)
    - Lettering, undated (Box 57)
    - General auditions - time slots, undated (Box 57)
    - ScriptShare, undated (Box 57)
    - Writers Executive Committee minutes, 1985 October 3 (Box 57)
    - Members' bulletin, 1985 October (Box 57)
    - Lost members, undated (Box 58)
    - Applications, 1950-1956; 22 (Box 58)
    - Applications, 1957-1963; 49 (Box 59)
    - Applications, 1964-1970; 37 (Box 60)
    - Applications, 1971-1976; 39 (Box 61)
    - Applications, 1977-1983; 27 (Box 62)
    - New Dramatists Admissions Committee report, 1983; 7 (Box 63)
    - Admission materials, 1982-1983; 14 (Box 63)
    - Admission materials, 1984; 16 (Box 64)
    - Admission materials, 1984; 2 (Box 65)
    - "Final Coronation" by Gallardo, undated (Box 65)
    - "Everybody Knows My Business" by Gallardo, Yolanda and Edward, undated (Box 65)
    - "Bernie" by Gallardo, Edward, undated (Box 65)
    - "Florida Girls" by Fitz-Hasty, Nancy (3 copies), 1981; 2 (Box 65)
    - "Alice and Fred" by Ellentuck, Dan, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 65)
    - "The Wonderful Tower of Humber Lavoignet" by Alvarez, Lynne, 1984 (Box 65)
    - "Sweet Dreams" by Hill, David J., 1981 (Box 65)
    - "Lucian's Woods" by Hill, David J., 1982 (Box 65)
    - "Swop" Jenkins, Ken, 1981 (Box 65)
    - "Waltz on a Merry-Go-Round" by Gallardo, Edward, undated (Box 65)
    - "Winterfire" by Gilhooley, Jack, 1982 (Box 65)
    - "Carrie and Nell..." by Dunn, Thomas G., 1983 (Box 65)
    - "Cheat" by Harrington, Laura, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Drawer lists, undated (Box 66)
    - Members guide to New Dramatists, undated (Box 66)
    - Staff and board, 1983-1984 (Box 66)
    - Actor's biographies, undated (Box 66)
    - "Slidescape" by Bigham, Abra (2 copies), 1981; 2 (Box 66)
    - "Fat Fell Down" by Ellentuck, Dan, 1978 (Box 66)
    - "Alice and Fred" by Ellentuck, Dan (2 copies), 1983; 2 (Box 66)
    - "Blood an' Kin" (working title) by Bigham, Abra, 1984 November (Box 66)
    - "Indiscretions" by Hill, David J., 1983 (Box 66)
    - "Town Portrait" by Hill, David J., 1980 (Box 66)
    - "Forklift" by Hobson, Richard, undated (Box 66)
    - "Overland Rooms" by Hobson, Richard, undated (Box 66)
    - "Memphis Is Gone" by Hobson, Richard, undated (Box 66)
    - Directors, undated; 6 (Box 66)
    - Exchanges, 1983-1986; 6 (Box 66)
    - IBM copier usage cards, 1984 (Box 66)
    - Long range planning committee, 1984 (Box 66)
    - Celebrity doodles auction cards, 1982 December 6 (Box 67)
    - Contact cards, undated (Box 67)
    - Receipts, undated; 7 (Box 67)
    - Receipts, undated; 8 (Box 68)
    - Petty cash, 1980 (Box 68)
    - McDonald's, 1986-1987; 6 (Box 68)
    - Celebrity doodle auction, 1983 (Box 68)
    - Taxes, 1987 (Box 69)
    - National Endowment for the Arts challenge grant, 1986 (Box 69)
    - Bank statements, 1988-1990 (Box 69)
    - Petty cash, 1980's; 2 (Box 69)
    - Checks and bank statements, 1981-1987; 4 (Box 69)
    - Applications, 1951-1972; 19 (Box 70)
    - Applications, 1966-1976; 17 (Box 71)
    - Applications, 1950-1981; 20 (Box 72)
    - General ledger, 1974 (Box 72)
    - Dunn, Thomas G. correspondence, 1985-1988; 9 (Box 73)
    - Royalty payments, 1985 (Box 73)
    - Financial statements, 1984-1990; 4 (Box 73)
    - Contact sheets, 1987-1988 (Box 73)
    - Ledger, 1975-1979 (Box 74)
    - Shows, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Lorraine Hansberry Project, 1983 (Box 74)
    - Hal Prince luncheon, 1988 May 10 (Box 74)
    - Applications, 1959-1973; 3 (Box 74)
    - Financial reports, 1956-1960 (Box 74)
    - Payroll cards, 1979; 2 (Box 74)
    - Cash disbursements journal, 1980 (Box 74)
    - Unidentified play, undated (Box 74)
    - Audits, 1958-1963 (Box 74)
    - Telephone logs and bills, 1982-1985 (Box 74)
    - Telephone logs and bills, 1982-1985; 2 (Box 75)
    - Cancelled checks, 1970s-1986; 4 (Box 75)
    - Petty Cash, 1982 (Box 76)
    - Deposit slips, 1970's-1980's; 2 (Box 76)
    - Applications, 1950-1979; 13 (Box 76)
    - Applications, 1950-1979; 17 (Box 77)
    - Applications, 1950-1979; 7 (Box 78)
    - Cancelled checks, 1984; 6 (Box 78)
    - Cancelled checks, 1984-1986; 5 (Box 79)
    - Executive director, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Literary expenses, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Workshop expenses, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Actor's expenses, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Printed ephemera and playbills, 1983-1985; 8 (Box 80)
    - Printed ephemera and playbills, 1984-1986; 4 (Box 81)
    - Industry drive, 1983-1984 (Box 81)
    - Wagener, Terri, 1980-1986 (Box 82)
    - L.A. Stage Company, 1980-1984 (Box 82)
    - Hippodrome Theatre, 1981-1984 (Box 82)
    - Los Angeles Public Theatre, 1981-1984 (Box 82)
    - The Next Theatre Company, 1982-1983 (Box 82)
    - Burnham Theatre Guild, 1982-1983 (Box 82)
    - Trinity Square Repertory Company, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - The Landers Theatre, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Playwrights' Workshop Montreal, 1982-1984 (Box 82)
    - Milwaukee Repertory Theatre, 1982-1985 (Box 82)
    - University of Nevada at Las Vegas, 1982-1985 (Box 82)
    - The University of Alabama Theatre, 1982-1985 (Box 82)
    - Theatre Memphis, 1982-1985 (Box 82)
    - Remains Theatre, 1982-1985 (Box 82)
    - Empire State Institute for the Performing Arts, 1982-1986 (Box 82)
    - Connecticut Theatre, 1982-1983 (Box 82)
    - The Independent Eye, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Geva Theatre, 1984-1986 (Box 82)
    - Invisible Theatre, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Academy Theatre, 1983 (Box 82)
    - Topel & Associates, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - The Road Company, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Kalamazoo Civic Players, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - The Iris Group, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Irondale Ensemble Project, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Great North American History, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - University of Minnesota, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Actors for Themselves, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Brass Tacks, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Pasadena Playhouse, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Center Stage, Hunterdon Arts Center, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Cherub's Guild, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Caldwell Playhouse, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - ScriptShare, 1986 (Box 82)
    - Pheasant Run Theatre, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - Old Globe Theatre, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - Waterloo Community Playhouse, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - Illusion Theatre, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - Asolo State Theatre, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - Ithaca College, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - The Empty Space, 1983-1985 (Box 82)
    - Pennsylvania Stage, 1983-1986 (Box 83)
    - Boarshead Theatre, 1983-1986 (Box 83)
    - Denver Center Productions, 1983-1986 (Box 83)
    - Philadelphia Drama Guild, 1983-1986 (Box 83)
    - Alliance Theatre Company, 1983-1986 (Box 83)
    - Seattle Children's Theatre, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Kenyon Festival Theatre, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Jomandi, 1984 (Box 83)
    - MCH Theatre, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Metropolitan Repertory Company, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Coconut Grove Playhouse, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Oregon Shakespeare, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Norman Twain Productions, 1984-1985 (Box 83)
    - Force Ten Productions, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 83)
    - Lindsey Enterprises, 1984-1985 (Box 83)
    - University of Miami, 1984-1985 (Box 83)
    - St. Ann Center, 1984-1986 (Box 83)
    - Arena Stage, 1984-1986 (Box 83)
    - City Players of St. Louis, 1984-1986 (Box 83)
    - WPA Theatre, 1984-1986 (Box 83)
    - Main Street Theatre, 1984-1986 (Box 83)
    - The Repertory Theatre of St. Louis, 1984-1986 (Box 83)
    - Virginia Museum Theatre, 1985 (Box 83)
    - Humboldt State University, 1985 (Box 83)
    - The Foundry Theatre Company, 1985 (Box 83)
    - Stormfield Theatre Company, 1985 (Box 83)
    - Blackhawk Enterprises, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Wheaton College, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - The Whole Theatre, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Missouri Repertory Theatre, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Stage #1, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Scholastic, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Chappaqua Drama Group, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Media Ventures, 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - Doodles auction, undated (Box 83)
    - On Stage, 1989 (Box 83)
    - Artwork - copies of doodles, undated (Box 83)
    - Anderson, Robert, 1983 (Box 83)
    - Xerox playbill, undated (Box 83)
    - Programs for playwrights, 1981 (Box 83)
    - Twenty-ninth anniversary luncheon, 1978 May 5 (Box 83)
    - Annual luncheon, 1979-1990; 10 (Box 83)
    - The Living Theatre, 1959-1960 (Box 83)
    - Workshop staging of "Down on the Farm", 1972 (Box 83)
    - The plan for playwrights, 1955 (Box 83)
    - On Stage, 1986 (Box 84)
    - Annual luncheon, 1984-1989; 2 (Box 84)
    - Board meeting tapes, 1985-1986 (Box 84)
    - Press
      - Tear sheets, 1950s (Box 84)
      - Press releases, 1985-1987 (Box 84)
      - Press - doodles auction, 1984 (Box 84)
      - Stagearts Theatre Company, 1984 (Box 84)
      - Press and reviews, 1986-1987; 5 (Box 84)
      - Literary managers and dramaturgs, 1984 (Box 84)
      - UPS, 1986 (Box 84)
      - Newsletter #3, 1986-1987 (Box 84)
      - Old newsletter materials, undated (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous press materials, undated (Box 84)
      - Newsletter publication information, undated (Box 84)
      - Shanley, John Patrick, undated (Box 84)
      - McIntyre, Dennis, 1979-1987 (Box 84)
      - Hill, David J., 1979-1986 (Box 84)
      - Schenkar, Joan, undated (Box 84)
      - Shanley, John Patrick, 1984-1985 (Box 84)
      - Steinbach, Victor, undated (Box 84)
      - Sweet, Jeffrey, 1983-1985 (Box 84)
      - Therriault, Daniel, 1986 (Box 84)
      - Wagner, Terri, 1984 (Box 84)
      - Wilson, August, 1986-1987; 2 (Box 84)
      - Wellman, John, 1984 (Box 84)
      - Yoshimura, Jim, 1984 (Box 84)
      - Zigun, Dick, 1982-1984 (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous press materials, undated (Box 84)
      - Members activities updates, 1984 (Box 84)
      - Television and film activities of members, 1985 (Box 84)
      - Original press book, 1983-1984 (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous press materials, undated (Box 84)
      - Harrington, Laura, 1985 (Box 85)
      - Heifner, Jack, 1985 (Box 85)
      - Jones, Jeffrey, 1982-1985 (Box 85)
      - Kesselman, Wendy, 1985-1986 (Box 85)
      - Kramer, Sherry, 1982 (Box 85)
      - Linney, Romulus, 1965-1982 (Box 85)
      - Lord, Robert, 1985 (Box 85)
      - Maguire, Matt, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Mann, Emily, 1984-1985 (Box 85)
      - McIntyre, Daniel, 1984-1985 (Box 85)
      - McLaughlin, Ellen, 1986 May (Box 85)
      - Nassivera, John, 1983-1985 (Box 85)
      - Nicholson, James, 1980-1987 (Box 85)
      - Olive, John, 1981-1985 (Box 85)
      - Overmeyer, Eric, 1985-1986 (Box 85)
      - Pielmeier, John, 1982-1985 (Box 85)
      - Pietri, Pedro Juan, 1984-1985 (Box 85)
      - Rosen, Sheldon, undated (Box 85)
      - Gray, Amlin, 1984-1985 (Box 85)
      - Giardina, Anthony, 1983 (Box 85)
      - Gallagher, Mary, 1980-1982 (Box 85)
      - Edwards, Gus, undated (Box 85)
      - Dresser, Richard, 1983 (Box 85)
      - Davis, Russel, undated (Box 85)
      - D'Andrea, Paul, 1982-1985 (Box 85)
      - Congdon, Connie, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Carter, Steve, 1982-1983 (Box 85)
      - Bowne, Alan, 1986-1987 (Box 85)
      - Alvarez, Lynne, undated (Box 85)
    - ScriptShare program
      - Correspondence, 15 (Box 85)
      - Brittan, Robert, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 85)
      - Readings, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 85)
      - Gilhooley, Jack, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Jones, Jeff, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Kramer, Sherry, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Cattaneo, Ann, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Gallagher, Mary, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Zigun, Dick, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Becker, Alma, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Theatre lists, 1983-1984 (Box 85)
      - Writers' fees, 1983 (Box 85)
      - Script report forms, undated (Box 85)
      - Admissions: recruitment, 1983 Fall; 2 (Box 85)
      - Becker, Alma, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Davis, Russell, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Levi, Stephen, 1984 (Box 85)
      - Maloney, Peter, 1984 (Box 85)
    - Postcard lists, undated; 2 (Box 85)
    - Subscription information, 1986-1987 (Box 85)
    - Weidner timelines, undated (Box 85)
    - Miscellaneous lists and correspondence, undated (Box 85)
    - Periodicals, 1987 (Box 85)
    - Literary department explanations, undated (Box 85)
    - Library, undated; 3 (Box 85)
    - Graphics, undated (Box 85)
    - Playbill - Stein, undated (Box 85)
    - Contact sheets, undated; 2 (Box 85)
    - McDonald's Literary Achievement Award, 1986; 5 (Box 85)
    - Reader's Agreement, undated (Box 85)
    - McDonald's award ceremony, 1986 (Box 86)
    - Applicant script log, undated (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982; 8 (Box 86)
    - Luncheon and drive, 1976; 3 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence, 1984; 2 (Box 86)
    - Industry drive, 1986; 2 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1989; 13 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 88)
    - Newsletters (Readings), 1985-1987 (Box 88)
    - Long range plan, 1988-1991 (Box 88)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1986-1988; 4 (Box 88)
    - Composer-librettist studio, undated (Box 88)
    - Postcards (masters), undated (Box 88)
    - Testimonials, 1990 (Box 88)
    - Development letters, undated (Box 88)
    - "Max Ehrenheart" by McGraw, Kathleen Patricia, 1989 (Box 88)
    - "What's on the Rail for the Lizard" by Nkosi, K. M., 1986 (Box 88)
    - "Two Below" by Robertson, George, undated (Box 88)
    - ScriptShare catalogue, 1987-1988 (Box 88)
    - "Stephen Fetchit: Uncle Tom, or Black Film Pioneer?" by Brown, Michael Henry, undated (Box 88)
    - Bulletins, 1985-1989; 14 (Box 88)
    - Lorraine Hansberry Gold Award, 1983 (Box 88)
    - Executive committee minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 88)
    - Actor lists, 1983-1984 (Box 88)
    - Kanin, Garson - stationery and signatures, undated (Box 89)
    - "Creditors" playbill, 1992 (Box 89)
    - Kazan, Elia - craft discussion, 1955 (Box 89)
    - Staged reading of "Last Night's Lightning" by Erickson, David M., 1981 (Box 89)
    - John Drew theatre project, 1990 (Box 89)
    - Monologue project, 1986 (Box 89)
    - One-act festival, 1984 (Box 89)
    - Jordan, June (NYSCA writer in residence), undated (Box 89)
    - Cast contact sheet, 1986 (Box 89)
    - Contribution receipts, undated (Box 89)
    - Printed scripts, undated (Box 89)
    - Playbills, undated (Box 89)
    - Luncheon playbills, 1986-1988 (Box 89)
    - New Dramatist flyers, undated (Box 89)
    - Mailgrams, 1988-1899 (Box 89)
    - Miscellaneous New Dramatists printed material, 1981-1987 (Box 89)
    - Staff lists, 1983-1987 (Box 89)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1982-1989; 10 (Box 89)
    - Doodles, 1983 (Box 89)
    - Publicity, 1984 (Box 89)
    - ScriptShare materials, undated (Box 89)
    - On Stage, 1989 (Box 89)
    - Monologue book - proofs, undated (Box 89)
    - Readings photos, undated (Box 89)
    - Press book, 1988-1989 (Box 89)
    - Insurance, undated (Box 90)
    - ScriptShare catalogue, 1988-1989 (Box 90)
    - Canada and England (miscellaneous), undated (Box 90)
    - Self publishing proposal, 1989 (Box 90)
    - Programs for plays, 1984 (Box 90)
    - Long range plan- miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 90)
    - Opera exchange and workshop, 1983 (Box 90)
    - Playwright Union of Canada, 1982-1988 (Box 90)
    - Services available, 1983 (Box 90)
    - Instruction manuals of office equipment, undated (Box 90)
    - Theatre lists, undated (Box 90)
    - Job information, undated (Box 90)
    - Los Angeles/west coast New Dramatists plans, 1984 (Box 90)
    - Word processor, 1983-1985 (Box 90)
    - Rooftop project, undated (Box 90)
    - Stein, Howard article, undated (Box 90)
    - National Endowment for the Arts theatre, 1984-1985 (Box 90)
    - National Endowment for the Arts opera musical, 1985-1986 (Box 90)
    - Jamaica, undated (Box 90)
    - Hansberry, Lorraine, 1982-1985; 2 (Box 90)
    - Housing - New York City proposal, undated (Box 90)
    - Tom Dunn
      - Memos, 1989; 6 (Box 90)
      - Financial records, undated (Box 90)
      - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 90)
    - Summerfare computer Rolodex, 1987-1989; 2 (Box 91)
    - Weissberger reader forms, undated; 7 (Box 91)
    - Thank you letters to script reader, undated (Box 91)
    - Return log, undated (Box 91)
    - Script log, 1988 (Box 91)
    - Check out lists, undated (Box 91)
    - List of playwrights, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
    - Out of town reader applications, 1990 (Box 91)
    - Dunn, Tom - notes, undated (Box 91)
    - Interns contacted, 1988-1989 (Box 91)
    - Fall interns, 1987 (Box 91)
    - Winter interns, 1987 (Box 91)
    - Intern worksheet, 1985 (Box 91)
    - Employee directory, 1986 (Box 91)
    - Staff biographies, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
    - Staff policy booklet, undated (Box 91)
    - Letters of agreement (employment), 1982-1984 (Box 91)
    - Job description, undated (Box 91)
    - Public relations possibilities, undated (Box 91)
    - Managing director, 1989 (Box 91)
    - Staff lists, 1987-1989 (Box 91)
    - Resumes, 1989-1990 (Box 91)
    - Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 91)
    - Applicants for associate director, 1987 (Box 91)
    - Office manger resumes, 1989 (Box 91)